netline.com 2019-08-27

# NetLine Privacy Policy - Successful B2B Marketers Start Here - B2B Content Syndication Lead Generation

NetLine Corporation, a provider of e-marketing and marketing automation technology and services, is committed to protecting Internet user privacy. Below you will find our privacy policies for: 

  * This website – www.netline.com – and the information collected through it
  * e-Marketing campaigns executed on behalf of our clients 

**NetLine.com Privacy Statement**   
NetLine is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Information Collection And Use**  
NetLine collects information from our users at several different points on our website, including: 

**Newsletters / Email Alerts**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. NetLine uses the information provided to fulfill your request for information and, in some cases, personalize the email content for you. All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe, and unsubscribe requests will be processed within minutes. 

**Information Requests**  
Our site's information request forms require your name and email address as well as additional information to help us determine your needs related to our solution. We use this information to contact you about your request. Unless you have elected otherwise, the email address you provide on an information request form will not be added to our opt-in newsletter / emailing list. 

**Surveys**  
From time-to-time, our site may request information from you via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, so you have a choice whether or not to disclose the information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code, occupation). 

**Special Offers**  
To take advantage of promotional offers (e.g. free white paper) available on this site, you may be asked to complete a registration form requiring your name, email address, and other demographic information. Participation in these special offers is completely voluntary, however, you may not be able to take advantage of the offer without providing the required information. Unless you have elected otherwise, the email address you provide on a special offer registration form will not be added to our opt-in newsletter / emailing list. 

**Links**  
We use email links on this site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments that you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly. We use the information collected to respond directly to your questions or comments. 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that NetLine is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by NetLine. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
NetLine does not use cookies on our website except to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website, like our Web-based reporting tool. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site; however, your access to some areas of our website may be limited. 

**Sensors**  
NetLine does not use sensors on this website but does include a coded sensor in all of its HTML-based email messages in order to determine your ability to receive HTML-based messages, as well as whether an HTML email message has been opened or previewed. If you cannot receive HTML, you will not receive a functioning sensor. 

**Security**  
NetLine has implemented generally accepted standards of technology security in order to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. Only authorized NetLine personnel and agents are provided access to personal information and certain databases containing non-personal information, and these employees have agreed to ensure confidentiality of this information. All of our employees are made aware of and are accountable for compliance with our privacy policy. 

**Choice / Opt-Out**  
Only users who sign up to receive communications from NetLine will receive email from us. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or email alerts, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the link within the email you receive or by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line in the email. If you experience difficulty opting out in either of these ways, email us at [optout_help@netline.com](mailto:optout_help@netline.com). 

**Privacy Shield**  
Netline is certified to the E.U.-U.S. and Switzerland-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom or Switzerland, as applicable, to the United States. To read our Privacy Shield policy, click here. 

**Policy Changes**  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the website. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy. If there is a material change to our privacy policy we will post notification on our homepage. If there is a material change to personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail and provide the ability to opt out of these new uses. 

**Client e-Marketing Campaigns**   
NetLine delivers permission-based electronic marketing campaigns, including newsletters, surveys, and product offerings on behalf of our clients. NetLine's role in supporting our clients may include hosting the actual collection site, delivery of email, tracking results of e-marketing campaigns, analysis of data, and transferring collected data back to the client. 

In some cases, NetLine stores database lists from our clients. These lists may contain email addresses, street address, contact information and other relevant information. Confidentiality of the client list is a top priority. NetLine is contractually bound to keep our clients' customer data private. A client's list is never shared with other clients, partners, etc., and is treated as an asset of our client. 

NetLine tracks if a recipient has the ability to support HTML email in their email client, as well as whether an HTML email message has been opened or previewed. This capability is used only to deliver the best content to the recipient, and the recipient always has control to change their profile by contacting the client for whom the campaign was deployed. 

Information regarding the activity of campaign recipients is only reported to the client who deployed the e-marketing campaign through NetLine. Information about specific campaign recipients is only shared with the client who owns the list on which the recipients email address originally appeared. 

NetLine has a strict policy against sending unsolicited commercial email. If problems arise with a client's campaign, NetLine will work with the client to resolve the problems and prevent them in the future. If NetLine determines that a client has knowingly used our system for sending unsolicited commercial email, NetLine will revoke the right of this client to send email from our system. 

If you no longer wish to receive email from a NetLine client, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the link within the email you receive or by contacting the client for whom the campaign was deployed directly. If you experience difficulty opting out in either of these ways, email us at [optout_help@netline.com](mailto:optout_help@netline.com).
